

I'm passionate & dedicated to my work with **2+** years' experience as a Web developer & **6Y 5M+** experience as Qlik Sense Expert.

I have acquired the skills and knowledge necessary to make your project a **success**. I enjoy every step of the **design** process, from discussion and **collaboration**.

Trainer in **Udemy**, have published 4 courses on Qlik Sense API learning.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+91 9594411469

WEBSITE:

https://ajaykakkar93.github.io/

EMAIL:

ajaykakkar93@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Cooking Music Movies RND

LINKS
Udemy, YouTube, LinkedIn,
GitHub

AJAY KAKKAR

Sr. Qlik Sense Developer

EDUCATION

St. John's The Evangelist High School 2008-09 SSC

Bagarka College

2010-11 HSC

MVLU College

2015 B.Sc. In Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

Clay Logix Qlik Developer

2016-20

Qlik API, Frontend & Backend

Medly Pharmacy Qlik Developer

2020-22

Qlik API, Frontend, Backend, NPrinting & QMC

Predoole Analytics Sr. Qlik Sense Developer

2022-Presen

Qlik API, Frontend, Backend, NPrinting, Products & RND

SKILLS

